championshipmanager.co.uk 2012-06-17

# Eidos.com - Privacy Statement

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Square Enix Limited ("we", “our”, “Square Enix” and similar expressions) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This document should be read in conjunction with our Terms and Conditions of Use, a copy of which can be found at **www.eidos.com/terms**. Words and phrases defined in the Terms and Conditions have the same meaning where used in this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy (together with our Terms and Conditions of Use and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us in connection with your use of our Website at www.eidos.com.

Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it..

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the “Act”), the data controller is Square Enix Limited of Wimbledon Bridge House, 1 Hartfield Road, London SW19 3RU, England.

All capitalised terms used but not defined in this Privacy Policy have the same meaning as given to such terms in our Terms and Conditions of Use. 

**1\. INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU**

We may collect and process the following information about you:

  * Information that you provide by opening an Account or which is otherwise provided at the time of registering as a User of any of our websites or those operated by our affiliates, subscribing to any Service, posting or uploading material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information if you enter any competitions or promotions and when you report a problem with our Website. 
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. 
  * We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them. 
  * Details of your visits to our Website including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access. 
  * Details of your personal interests and preferences of which you inform us when you complete forms or answer questions when registering to use our Website. 
  * Details about your on-line activity including data, statistics and information relating to your game usage and game play including (for example) your scores, rankings, and achievements. 

**2\. IP ADDRESSES AND COOKIES**

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our Users' and guests’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual. We may also use IP addresses to personally identify you in order to enforce our Terms and Conditions of Use and we may block certain IP addresses from accessing or all any part of our Website or Services in the event of a user abuse.

For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalised service. They enable us:

  * To identify where our Website is being accessed from; 
  * estimate our audience size and usage pattern. 
  * To store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise our Website according to your individual interests. • To speed up your searches. 
  * To recognise you when you return to our Website. 

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our Website.

Please note that our advertisers or third party websites which may be linked to or accessible via our Website may also use cookies, over which we have no control.

**3\. WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

All information you provide to us is stored on secure servers hosted by us or third parties providing hosting, payment, order fulfillment or other services for us. Any payment transactions will be encrypted. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Website; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

**4\. USES MADE OF THE INFORMATION**

PLEASE NOTE, AS A CONDITION OF REGISTERING FOR AN ACCOUNT WITH US, YOU MUST AGREE TO RECEIVING TARGETED ON-SCREEN ADVERTISING AS OUTLINED BELOW. IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO RECEIVE THIS, DO NOT REGISTER FOR OUR WEBSITE.

We use information held about you in the following ways:

To ensure that content from our Website is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.

To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.

To target on-screen advertising from our advertisers, tailored for you based on information and details you have given to us in the process of registering to use our Website.

To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.

To allow you to use or participate in any Services including Interactive Services.

To compile game metrics and other records and statistics for display on our Website including but not limited to statistics and achievements of Users playing our games.

To notify you about changes to our services; and

for any purpose for which we are granted the right to use your information or which is otherwise specified under the Terms and Conditions.

FURTHER, CERTAIN INFORMATION ABOUT YOU WHICH YOU DECIDE TO MAKE AVAILABLE FOR OTHER REGISTERED USERS OF OUR WEBSITE TO SEE, WILL BE DISPLAYED ON YOUR PROFILE PAGE IN PROXIMITY TO YOUR AVATAR. YOU SHOULD ONLY THEREFORE PROVIDE SUCH DATA AS YOU ARE ENTIRELY COMFORTABLE WITH PROVIDING AND WE STRONGLY RECOMMEND THAT YOU DO NOT PROVIDE DETAILS SUCH AS A HOME OR OFFICE ADDRESS OR CONTACT DETAILS, PHOTOGRAPHS OR OTHER CONTACT INFORMATION WHICH COULD BE USED TO MAKE PERSONAL CONTACT WITH YOU. YOU MAY CHANGE SUCH INFORMATION AT ANY TIME BY CLICKING ON THE 'EDIT ACCOUNT INFO' BUTTON ON YOUR PROFILE PAGE.

We may also use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these by post or telephone.

If you are an existing customer, we may only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you.

If you are a new customer, and where we permit selected third parties to use your data, we (or they) may contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this.

Before we use your data in this way, we will notify you and/or provide you with a series of tick box options during registration. If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data (the registration form).

We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we may provide them with anonymised and/or aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 500 men aged under 30 have clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such anonymised and/or aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target (for example, women in SW1). We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers' wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience.

**5\. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group whether based within or outside of the European Economic Area, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.

If we or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.

If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms of Sale and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of us, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**6\. YOUR RIGHTS**

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes, although if you want to register to use our Website, you must accept that you will allow certain on-screen advertising, tailored to you as a condition of registration. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at [**privacy@square-enix.com**](mailto:privacy@square-enix.com)

Our Website may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

**7\. ACCESS TO INFORMATION**

****The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

**8\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

Any changes we may make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.

**9\. CONTACT**

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [**privacy@square-enix.com**](mailto:privacy@square-enix.com)

**10\. LAW**

This Privacy Policy is to be construed in accordance with the laws of England.
